NABIL FANNANE

+1 (415) 574-7713 <u>mzabi30@gmail.com</u> https://mzabicoder.github.io/react-portfolio-2024/

I am passionate lifelong learner seeking success in the field of Web Development. I have 3.5 years of experience in Front-End engineering. I am taking my tech skills, primarily centered around nimble learning and adaptation to full stack web apps

Technical Skills

- ✓ HTML/CSS/SASS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ FlexBox/Grid
- ✓ TypeScript

- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ React/Angular
- ✓ ExpressJS
- ✓ Mongoose
- ✓ NodeJS/Jest
- ✓ NPM/Yarn/Git/GitHub
- ✓ MongoDB/PostgreSQL
- ✓ MaterializeCSS/Reactstrap/Material-UI

EXPERIENCE

IBM - Since September 2021

UI Engineer

San Jose, CA,

- Implement features and bug fixes for automation service that IBM Waston Studio/ Elyra relies on, to provide quality quality software https://elyra-ai.github.io/canvas/#elyra-canvas-modules.
- Build and enhance tools to support developer productivity, and robust development services.
- Communicate ideas effectively to fellow team members, and business stakeholders through technical assessments, scrum meetings, demos, etc.

Costar Group (Nov 2020 – August 2021)

San Francisco, CA,

Front End Engineer

- Handle user stories & tasks Using Azure (TFS)
- Create reusable modules & components for re-platforming www.bizbuysell.com
- Par Create detailed documentations for new features.

INFOMATUM LLC (Jun 2014 – Oct 2017)

San Francisco, CA

IT&Web Analyst

- Co-working venues and display pictures & information about them upon click
- Design the layout and visual of the site using (CSS3,Grid,Flex,Bootstrap)
- Part of a 3-member team providing IT solutions to small business clients across the Bay Area
- Install, configure and troubleshoot network-level WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity , DNS, DHCP, VPN
- Imaging new PCs with Acronix and MACs with Deploy-studio, Manage & set up Duo two-factor authentification

ATTACK!! (Nov 2011- Oct 2013)

San Francisco, CA

Desktop Engineer

- Member of in-house IT team for a relationship marketing company with offices in California andNew York
- Install, configure and troubleshoot laptops, workstations, printers and IP-phones. Manageandset up Cisco phone users
- Troubleshoot and configure DNS, DHCP, VPN, HTTP ,AD administration Windows server 2003/2008,Windows XP/7/8, Thunderbird, Outlook, Google Applications and Office 2010
- Configure & troublshoot WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity including remote connection using LogmeIn,gotomeeting
- Create and maintain user accounts, passwords, data integrity, system access and security fordesktop technologies

STMicroelectronics (Sep2009–jun2011)

Casa, Morocco

Production Engineer

- Co-working venues and display pictures & information about them upon click
- Design the layout and visual of the site using (CSS3,Grid,Flex,Bootstrap)
- Part of a 3-member team providing IT solutions to small business clients across the Bay Area
- Install, configure and troubleshoot network-level WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity, DNS, DHCP,VPN
- Imaging new PCs with Acronix and MACs with Deploy-studio, Manage & set up Duo two-factor authenti

EDUCATION

MOROCCAN SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING

Casa, Morocco